Paulo! No walking tour today?
Paulo! 今天没有徒步旅行吗?
Not for me.
我没去.
Won't Didi miss you?
Didi不会挂念你吗?
Sh. Let them go.
Sh. 让他们去吧.
What about all the sights?
景点怎么办啊?
I've seen the sights.
我都看过了
The gardens, the monuments, the famous halls.
花园,纪念碑和著名的礼堂.
They're all very interesting.
这些都很值得一看.
But I'm very tired.
不过我实在太累了.
Didi does cover a lot of ground.
Didi确实很能走.
The woman never stops moving.
这个女人从不停下.
Today, it's museums. Tomorrow, famous libraries.
今天去博物馆,明天去著名的图书馆.
The next day, I don't know, statues maybe.
后天,我不知道,可能是雕像.
I hate walking! Do you know what I like, Kevin?
我讨厌走路! 你知道我喜欢什么吗,Kevin?
Beaches. I like the beach.
海滩. 我喜欢海滩.
For my vacation, I like to lie on the beach and relax.
度假时,我喜欢躺在海滩上放松.
You'd like Cape Cod then.
那你会喜欢科德角半岛(Cape Cod).
The Cape's got beautiful beaches and dunes and islands.
那儿有美丽的海滩, 沙丘和小岛.
Is it far away?
离这里远吗?
By car?
开车吗?
No, on foot. With Didi, we walk!
不, 走着去. 和Didi在一起我们就得走路!